Okay. Um what we're going to do is we're
going to actually cover how to access
both local storage and session storage.
And we're just going to follow um the
same CRUD functionality that I talked
about previously. So I'm going to show
you how to create items, retrieve items,
update items, and delete items. So to do
that, what I'm going to do is I'm going
to come here and I'm going to say let's
add an item to local storage. The way
you do that is you say local storage do
set item and then you give it a key. and
I'm gonna say hello and then I'm going
to set the value to world. If I hit
enter, it returns undefined. But now if
I come over here to application and I
click on local storage, you can see that
the key is hello and the value is world.
Um, so I have now stored something
successfully in local storage. The way
you store something in session storage
is very similar. So you'd say session
storage set item and we'll also set
hello
and world.
And now if we look at our application um
here in session storage we have hello
and world. And the great thing about
this is if I reload my page um if I come
to my console it still prints out one
and everything else is gone. So you can
see I reloaded the page. But if I come
here to application, my local storage is
still storing hello and world. And my
session storage is storing hello and
world as well. So the key is hello, the
value is world. And that's how you add
something to local and session